[
    {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "１・へや",
        "correct_answer": "ひとつ",
        "other_answers": [
            "いちだい",
            "いちまい",
            "ひとり",
            "いっしゅうかん",
            "いっかげつ",
            "いっかい",
            "いちねん",
            "いちにち",
            "いっぱい",
            "いっさつ",
            "いっぽん",
            "いっぴき",
            "いっとう",
            "いちわ",
            "いちじかん",
            "いっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "２・かばん",
        "correct_answer": "ふたつ",
        "other_answers": [
            "にだい",
            "にまい",
            "ふたり",
            "にじゅうかん",
            "にかげつ",
            "にかい",
            "にねん",
            "ふつか",
            "にはい",
            "にさつ",
            "にほん",
            "にひき",
            "にとう",
            "にわ",
            "にじかん",
            "にふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "３・たまご",
        "correct_answer": "みっつ",
        "other_answers": [
            "さんだい",
            "さんまい",
            "さんにん",
            "さんしゅうかん",
            "さんかげつ",
            "さんかい",
            "さんねん",
            "みっか",
            "さんばい",
            "さんさつ",
            "さんぼん",
            "さんびき",
            "さんとう",
            "さんわ",
            "さんじかん",
            "さんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "４・へや",
        "correct_answer": "よっつ",
        "other_answers": [
            "よんだい",
            "よんまい",
            "よにん",
            "よんじゅうかん",
            "よんかげつ",
            "よんかい",
            "よんねん",
            "よっか",
            "よんはい",
            "よんさつ",
            "よんほん",
            "よんひき",
            "よんとう",
            "よんわ",
            "よじかん",
            "よんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "５・かばん",
        "correct_answer": "いつつ",
        "other_answers": [
            "ごだい",
            "ごまい",
            "ごにん",
            "ごじゅうかん",
            "ごかげつ",
            "ごかい",
            "ごねん",
            "いつか",
            "ごはい",
            "ごさつ",
            "ごほん",
            "ごひき",
            "ごとう",
            "ごわ",
            "ごじかん",
            "ごふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "６・みかん",
        "correct_answer": "むっつ",
        "other_answers": [
            "ろくだい",
            "ろくまい",
            "ろくにん",
            "ろくしゅうかん",
            "ろっかげつ",
            "ろっかい",
            "ろくねん",
            "むいか",
            "ろっぱい",
            "ろくさつ",
            "ろっぽん",
            "ろっぴき",
            "ろくとう",
            "ろくわ",
            "ろくじかん",
            "ろくぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "７・みかん",
        "correct_answer": "ななつ",
        "other_answers": [
            "ななだい",
            "ななまい",
            "ななにん・しちにん",
            "ななしゅうかん",
            "ななかげつ・しちかげつ",
            "ななかい",
            "ななねん",
            "なのか",
            "ななはい",
            "ななさつ",
            "ななほん",
            "ななひき",
            "ななとう",
            "ななわ",
            "しちじかん",
            "ななふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "８・たまご",
        "correct_answer": "やっつ",
        "other_answers": [
            "はちだい",
            "はちまい",
            "はちにん",
            "はっしゅうかん",
            "はっかげつ",
            "はっかい",
            "はちねん",
            "ようか",
            "はっぱい",
            "はっさつ",
            "はっぽん",
            "はっぴき",
            "はっとう",
            "はちわ",
            "はちじかん",
            "はっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "９・へや",
        "correct_answer": "ここのつ",
        "other_answers": [
            "きゅうだい",
            "きゅうまい",
            "きゅうにん",
            "きゅうしゅうかん",
            "きゅうかげつ",
            "きゅうかい",
            "きゅうねん",
            "ここのか",
            "きゅうはい",
            "きゅうさつ",
            "きゅうほん",
            "きゅうひき",
            "きゅうとう",
            "きゅうわ",
            "くじかん",
            "きゅうふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "１０・へや",
        "correct_answer": "とお",
        "other_answers": [
            "じゅうだい",
            "じゅうまい",
            "じゅうにん",
            "じゅっしゅうかん",
            "じゅっかげつ",
            "じゅっかい",
            "じゅうねん",
            "とおか",
            "じっぱい",
            "じっさつ",
            "じっぽん",
            "じっぴき",
            "じっとう",
            "じゅうわ",
            "じゅうじかん",
            "しゅうっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "？・かばん",
        "correct_answer": "いくつ",
        "other_answers": [
            "なんだい",
            "なんまい",
            "なんにん",
            "なんしゅうかん",
            "なんかげつ",
            "なんかい",
            "なんねん",
            "なんにち",
            "なんばい",
            "なんさつ",
            "なんぼん",
            "なんびき",
            "なんとう",
            "なんわ",
            "なんじかん",
            "なんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "１・じてんしゃ",
        "correct_answer": "いちだい",
        "other_answers": [
            "ひとつ",
            "いちまい",
            "ひとり",
            "いっしゅうかん",
            "いっかげつ",
            "いっかい",
            "いちねん",
            "いちにち",
            "いっぱい",
            "いっさつ",
            "いっぽん",
            "いっぴき",
            "いっとう",
            "いちわ",
            "いちじかん",
            "いっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "２・じてんしゃ",
        "correct_answer": "にだい",
        "other_answers": [
            "ふたつ",
            "にまい",
            "ふたり",
            "にじゅうかん",
            "にかげつ",
            "にかい",
            "にねん",
            "ふつか",
            "にはい",
            "にさつ",
            "にほん",
            "にひき",
            "にとう",
            "にわ",
            "にじかん",
            "にふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "３・パソコン",
        "correct_answer": "さんだい",
        "other_answers": [
            "みっつ",
            "さんまい",
            "さんにん",
            "さんしゅうかん",
            "さんかげつ",
            "さんかい",
            "さんねん",
            "みっか",
            "さんばい",
            "さんさつ",
            "さんぼん",
            "さんびき",
            "さんとう",
            "さんわ",
            "さんじかん",
            "さんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "４・じてんしゃ",
        "correct_answer": "よんだい",
        "other_answers": [
            "よっつ",
            "よんまい",
            "よにん",
            "よんじゅうかん",
            "よんかげつ",
            "よんかい",
            "よんねん",
            "よっか",
            "よんはい",
            "よんさつ",
            "よんほん",
            "よんひき",
            "よんとう",
            "よんわ",
            "よじかん",
            "よんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "question": "５・テレビ",
        "correct_answer": "ごだい",
        "other_answers": [
            "いつつ",
            "ごまい",
            "ごにん",
            "ごじゅうかん",
            "ごかげつ",
            "ごかい",
            "ごねん",
            "いつか",
            "ごはい",
            "ごさつ",
            "ごほん",
            "ごひき",
            "ごとう",
            "ごわ",
            "ごじかん",
            "ごふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 16,
        "question": "６・じてんしゃ",
        "correct_answer": "ろくだい",
        "other_answers": [
            "むっつ",
            "ろくまい",
            "ろくにん",
            "ろくしゅうかん",
            "ろっかげつ",
            "ろっかい",
            "ろくねん",
            "むいか",
            "ろっぱい",
            "ろくさつ",
            "ろっぽん",
            "ろっぴき",
            "ろくとう",
            "ろくわ",
            "ろくじかん",
            "ろくぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 17,
        "question": "７・テレビ",
        "correct_answer": "ななだい",
        "other_answers": [
            "ななつ",
            "ななまい",
            "ななにん・しちにん",
            "ななしゅうかん",
            "ななかげつ・しちかげつ",
            "ななかい",
            "ななねん",
            "なのか",
            "ななはい",
            "ななさつ",
            "ななほん",
            "ななひき",
            "ななとう",
            "ななわ",
            "しちじかん",
            "ななふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 18,
        "question": "８・くるま",
        "correct_answer": "はちだい",
        "other_answers": [
            "やっつ",
            "はちまい",
            "はちにん",
            "はっしゅうかん",
            "はっかげつ",
            "はっかい",
            "はちねん",
            "ようか",
            "はっぱい",
            "はっさつ",
            "はっぽん",
            "はっぴき",
            "はっとう",
            "はちわ",
            "はちじかん",
            "はっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 19,
        "question": "９・じてんしゃ",
        "correct_answer": "きゅうだい",
        "other_answers": [
            "ここのつ",
            "きゅうまい",
            "きゅうにん",
            "きゅうしゅうかん",
            "きゅうかげつ",
            "きゅうかい",
            "きゅうねん",
            "ここのか",
            "きゅうはい",
            "きゅうさつ",
            "きゅうほん",
            "きゅうひき",
            "きゅうとう",
            "きゅうわ",
            "くじかん",
            "きゅうふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 20,
        "question": "１０・くるま",
        "correct_answer": "じゅうだい",
        "other_answers": [
            "とお",
            "じゅうまい",
            "じゅうにん",
            "じゅっしゅうかん",
            "じゅっかげつ",
            "じゅっかい",
            "じゅうねん",
            "とおか",
            "じっぱい",
            "じっさつ",
            "じっぽん",
            "じっぴき",
            "じっとう",
            "じゅうわ",
            "じゅうじかん",
            "しゅうっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 21,
        "question": "？・テレビ",
        "correct_answer": "なんだい",
        "other_answers": [
            "いくつ",
            "なんまい",
            "なんにん",
            "なんしゅうかん",
            "なんかげつ",
            "なんかい",
            "なんねん",
            "なんにち",
            "なんばい",
            "なんさつ",
            "なんぼん",
            "なんびき",
            "なんとう",
            "なんわ",
            "なんじかん",
            "なんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 22,
        "question": "１・シャツ",
        "correct_answer": "いちまい",
        "other_answers": [
            "ひとつ",
            "いちだい",
            "ひとり",
            "いっしゅうかん",
            "いっかげつ",
            "いっかい",
            "いちねん",
            "いちにち",
            "いっぱい",
            "いっさつ",
            "いっぽん",
            "いっぴき",
            "いっとう",
            "いちわ",
            "いちじかん",
            "いっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 23,
        "question": "２・ふうとう",
        "correct_answer": "にまい",
        "other_answers": [
            "ふたつ",
            "にだい",
            "ふたり",
            "にじゅうかん",
            "にかげつ",
            "にかい",
            "にねん",
            "ふつか",
            "にはい",
            "にさつ",
            "にほん",
            "にひき",
            "にとう",
            "にわ",
            "にじかん",
            "にふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 24,
        "question": "３・かみ",
        "correct_answer": "さんまい",
        "other_answers": [
            "みっつ",
            "さんだい",
            "さんにん",
            "さんしゅうかん",
            "さんかげつ",
            "さんかい",
            "さんねん",
            "みっか",
            "さんばい",
            "さんさつ",
            "さんぼん",
            "さんびき",
            "さんとう",
            "さんわ",
            "さんじかん",
            "さんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 25,
        "question": "４・ふうとう",
        "correct_answer": "よんまい",
        "other_answers": [
            "よっつ",
            "よんだい",
            "よにん",
            "よんじゅうかん",
            "よんかげつ",
            "よんかい",
            "よんねん",
            "よっか",
            "よんはい",
            "よんさつ",
            "よんほん",
            "よんひき",
            "よんとう",
            "よんわ",
            "よじかん",
            "よんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 26,
        "question": "５・シャツ",
        "correct_answer": "ごまい",
        "other_answers": [
            "いつつ",
            "ごだい",
            "ごにん",
            "ごじゅうかん",
            "ごかげつ",
            "ごかい",
            "ごねん",
            "いつか",
            "ごはい",
            "ごさつ",
            "ごほん",
            "ごひき",
            "ごとう",
            "ごわ",
            "ごじかん",
            "ごふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 27,
        "question": "６・ＣＤ",
        "correct_answer": "ろくまい",
        "other_answers": [
            "むっつ",
            "ろくだい",
            "ろくにん",
            "ろくしゅうかん",
            "ろっかげつ",
            "ろっかい",
            "ろくねん",
            "むいか",
            "ろっぱい",
            "ろくさつ",
            "ろっぽん",
            "ろっぴき",
            "ろくとう",
            "ろくわ",
            "ろくじかん",
            "ろくぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 28,
        "question": "７・てがみ",
        "correct_answer": "ななまい",
        "other_answers": [
            "ななつ",
            "ななだい",
            "ななにん・しちにん",
            "ななしゅうかん",
            "ななかげつ・しちかげつ",
            "ななかい",
            "ななねん",
            "なのか",
            "ななはい",
            "ななさつ",
            "ななほん",
            "ななひき",
            "ななとう",
            "ななわ",
            "しちじかん",
            "ななふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 29,
        "question": "８・ふうとう",
        "correct_answer": "はちまい",
        "other_answers": [
            "やっつ",
            "はちだい",
            "はちにん",
            "はっしゅうかん",
            "はっかげつ",
            "はっかい",
            "はちねん",
            "ようか",
            "はっぱい",
            "はっさつ",
            "はっぽん",
            "はっぴき",
            "はっとう",
            "はちわ",
            "はちじかん",
            "はっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 30,
        "question": "９・てがみ",
        "correct_answer": "きゅうまい",
        "other_answers": [
            "ここのつ",
            "きゅうだい",
            "きゅうにん",
            "きゅうしゅうかん",
            "きゅうかげつ",
            "きゅうかい",
            "きゅうねん",
            "ここのか",
            "きゅうはい",
            "きゅうさつ",
            "きゅうほん",
            "きゅうひき",
            "きゅうとう",
            "きゅうわ",
            "くじかん",
            "きゅうふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 31,
        "question": "１０・ふうとう",
        "correct_answer": "じゅうまい",
        "other_answers": [
            "とお",
            "じゅうだい",
            "じゅうにん",
            "じゅっしゅうかん",
            "じゅっかげつ",
            "じゅっかい",
            "じゅうねん",
            "とおか",
            "じっぱい",
            "じっさつ",
            "じっぽん",
            "じっぴき",
            "じっとう",
            "じゅうわ",
            "じゅうじかん",
            "しゅうっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 32,
        "question": "？・シャツ",
        "correct_answer": "なんまい",
        "other_answers": [
            "いくつ",
            "なんだい",
            "なんにん",
            "なんしゅうかん",
            "なんかげつ",
            "なんかい",
            "なんねん",
            "なんにち",
            "なんばい",
            "なんさつ",
            "なんぼん",
            "なんびき",
            "なんとう",
            "なんわ",
            "なんじかん",
            "なんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 33,
        "question": "１・こどもの",
        "correct_answer": "ひとり",
        "other_answers": [
            "ひとつ",
            "いちだい",
            "いちまい",
            "いっしゅうかん",
            "いっかげつ",
            "いっかい",
            "いちねん",
            "いちにち",
            "いっぱい",
            "いっさつ",
            "いっぽん",
            "いっぴき",
            "いっとう",
            "いちわ",
            "いちじかん",
            "いっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 34,
        "question": "２・こどもの",
        "correct_answer": "ふたり",
        "other_answers": [
            "ふたつ",
            "にだい",
            "にまい",
            "にじゅうかん",
            "にかげつ",
            "にかい",
            "にねん",
            "ふつか",
            "にはい",
            "にさつ",
            "にほん",
            "にひき",
            "にとう",
            "にわ",
            "にじかん",
            "にふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 35,
        "question": "３・こどもの",
        "correct_answer": "さんにん",
        "other_answers": [
            "みっつ",
            "さんだい",
            "さんまい",
            "さんしゅうかん",
            "さんかげつ",
            "さんかい",
            "さんねん",
            "みっか",
            "さんばい",
            "さんさつ",
            "さんぼん",
            "さんびき",
            "さんとう",
            "さんわ",
            "さんじかん",
            "さんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 36,
        "question": "４・こどもの",
        "correct_answer": "よにん",
        "other_answers": [
            "よっつ",
            "よんだい",
            "よんまい",
            "よんじゅうかん",
            "よんかげつ",
            "よんかい",
            "よんねん",
            "よっか",
            "よんはい",
            "よんさつ",
            "よんほん",
            "よんひき",
            "よんとう",
            "よんわ",
            "よじかん",
            "よんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 37,
        "question": "５・こどもの",
        "correct_answer": "ごにん",
        "other_answers": [
            "いつつ",
            "ごだい",
            "ごまい",
            "ごじゅうかん",
            "ごかげつ",
            "ごかい",
            "ごねん",
            "いつか",
            "ごはい",
            "ごさつ",
            "ごほん",
            "ごひき",
            "ごとう",
            "ごわ",
            "ごじかん",
            "ごふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 38,
        "question": "６・こどもの",
        "correct_answer": "ろくにん",
        "other_answers": [
            "むっつ",
            "ろくだい",
            "ろくまい",
            "ろくしゅうかん",
            "ろっかげつ",
            "ろっかい",
            "ろくねん",
            "むいか",
            "ろっぱい",
            "ろくさつ",
            "ろっぽん",
            "ろっぴき",
            "ろくとう",
            "ろくわ",
            "ろくじかん",
            "ろくぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 39,
        "question": "７・こどもの",
        "correct_answer": "ななにん・しちにん",
        "other_answers": [
            "ななつ",
            "ななだい",
            "ななまい",
            "ななしゅうかん",
            "ななかげつ・しちかげつ",
            "ななかい",
            "ななねん",
            "なのか",
            "ななはい",
            "ななさつ",
            "ななほん",
            "ななひき",
            "ななとう",
            "ななわ",
            "しちじかん",
            "ななふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 40,
        "question": "８・こどもの",
        "correct_answer": "はちにん",
        "other_answers": [
            "やっつ",
            "はちだい",
            "はちまい",
            "はっしゅうかん",
            "はっかげつ",
            "はっかい",
            "はちねん",
            "ようか",
            "はっぱい",
            "はっさつ",
            "はっぽん",
            "はっぴき",
            "はっとう",
            "はちわ",
            "はちじかん",
            "はっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 41,
        "question": "９・こどもの",
        "correct_answer": "きゅうにん",
        "other_answers": [
            "ここのつ",
            "きゅうだい",
            "きゅうまい",
            "きゅうしゅうかん",
            "きゅうかげつ",
            "きゅうかい",
            "きゅうねん",
            "ここのか",
            "きゅうはい",
            "きゅうさつ",
            "きゅうほん",
            "きゅうひき",
            "きゅうとう",
            "きゅうわ",
            "くじかん",
            "きゅうふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 42,
        "question": "１０・こどもの",
        "correct_answer": "じゅうにん",
        "other_answers": [
            "とお",
            "じゅうだい",
            "じゅうまい",
            "じゅっしゅうかん",
            "じゅっかげつ",
            "じゅっかい",
            "じゅうねん",
            "とおか",
            "じっぱい",
            "じっさつ",
            "じっぽん",
            "じっぴき",
            "じっとう",
            "じゅうわ",
            "じゅうじかん",
            "しゅうっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 43,
        "question": "？・こどもの",
        "correct_answer": "なんにん",
        "other_answers": [
            "いくつ",
            "なんだい",
            "なんまい",
            "なんしゅうかん",
            "なんかげつ",
            "なんかい",
            "なんねん",
            "なんにち",
            "なんばい",
            "なんさつ",
            "なんぼん",
            "なんびき",
            "なんとう",
            "なんわ",
            "なんじかん",
            "なんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 44,
        "question": "１・じゅうかん",
        "correct_answer": "いっしゅうかん",
        "other_answers": [
            "ひとつ",
            "いちだい",
            "いちまい",
            "ひとり",
            "いっかげつ",
            "いっかい",
            "いちねん",
            "いちにち",
            "いっぱい",
            "いっさつ",
            "いっぽん",
            "いっぴき",
            "いっとう",
            "いちわ",
            "いちじかん",
            "いっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 45,
        "question": "２・じゅうかん",
        "correct_answer": "にじゅうかん",
        "other_answers": [
            "ふたつ",
            "にだい",
            "にまい",
            "ふたり",
            "にかげつ",
            "にかい",
            "にねん",
            "ふつか",
            "にはい",
            "にさつ",
            "にほん",
            "にひき",
            "にとう",
            "にわ",
            "にじかん",
            "にふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 46,
        "question": "３・じゅうかん",
        "correct_answer": "さんしゅうかん",
        "other_answers": [
            "みっつ",
            "さんだい",
            "さんまい",
            "さんにん",
            "さんかげつ",
            "さんかい",
            "さんねん",
            "みっか",
            "さんばい",
            "さんさつ",
            "さんぼん",
            "さんびき",
            "さんとう",
            "さんわ",
            "さんじかん",
            "さんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 47,
        "question": "４・じゅうかん",
        "correct_answer": "よんじゅうかん",
        "other_answers": [
            "よっつ",
            "よんだい",
            "よんまい",
            "よにん",
            "よんかげつ",
            "よんかい",
            "よんねん",
            "よっか",
            "よんはい",
            "よんさつ",
            "よんほん",
            "よんひき",
            "よんとう",
            "よんわ",
            "よじかん",
            "よんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 48,
        "question": "５・じゅうかん",
        "correct_answer": "ごじゅうかん",
        "other_answers": [
            "いつつ",
            "ごだい",
            "ごまい",
            "ごにん",
            "ごかげつ",
            "ごかい",
            "ごねん",
            "いつか",
            "ごはい",
            "ごさつ",
            "ごほん",
            "ごひき",
            "ごとう",
            "ごわ",
            "ごじかん",
            "ごふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 49,
        "question": "６・じゅうかん",
        "correct_answer": "ろくしゅうかん",
        "other_answers": [
            "むっつ",
            "ろくだい",
            "ろくまい",
            "ろくにん",
            "ろっかげつ",
            "ろっかい",
            "ろくねん",
            "むいか",
            "ろっぱい",
            "ろくさつ",
            "ろっぽん",
            "ろっぴき",
            "ろくとう",
            "ろくわ",
            "ろくじかん",
            "ろくぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 50,
        "question": "７・じゅうかん",
        "correct_answer": "ななしゅうかん",
        "other_answers": [
            "ななつ",
            "ななだい",
            "ななまい",
            "ななにん・しちにん",
            "ななかげつ・しちかげつ",
            "ななかい",
            "ななねん",
            "なのか",
            "ななはい",
            "ななさつ",
            "ななほん",
            "ななひき",
            "ななとう",
            "ななわ",
            "しちじかん",
            "ななふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 51,
        "question": "８・じゅうかん",
        "correct_answer": "はっしゅうかん",
        "other_answers": [
            "やっつ",
            "はちだい",
            "はちまい",
            "はちにん",
            "はっかげつ",
            "はっかい",
            "はちねん",
            "ようか",
            "はっぱい",
            "はっさつ",
            "はっぽん",
            "はっぴき",
            "はっとう",
            "はちわ",
            "はちじかん",
            "はっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 52,
        "question": "９・じゅうかん",
        "correct_answer": "きゅうしゅうかん",
        "other_answers": [
            "ここのつ",
            "きゅうだい",
            "きゅうまい",
            "きゅうにん",
            "きゅうかげつ",
            "きゅうかい",
            "きゅうねん",
            "ここのか",
            "きゅうはい",
            "きゅうさつ",
            "きゅうほん",
            "きゅうひき",
            "きゅうとう",
            "きゅうわ",
            "くじかん",
            "きゅうふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 53,
        "question": "１０・じゅうかん",
        "correct_answer": "じゅっしゅうかん",
        "other_answers": [
            "とお",
            "じゅうだい",
            "じゅうまい",
            "じゅうにん",
            "じゅっかげつ",
            "じゅっかい",
            "じゅうねん",
            "とおか",
            "じっぱい",
            "じっさつ",
            "じっぽん",
            "じっぴき",
            "じっとう",
            "じゅうわ",
            "じゅうじかん",
            "しゅうっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 54,
        "question": "？・じゅうかん",
        "correct_answer": "なんしゅうかん",
        "other_answers": [
            "いくつ",
            "なんだい",
            "なんまい",
            "なんにん",
            "なんかげつ",
            "なんかい",
            "なんねん",
            "なんにち",
            "なんばい",
            "なんさつ",
            "なんぼん",
            "なんびき",
            "なんとう",
            "なんわ",
            "なんじかん",
            "なんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 55,
        "question": "１・かげつ",
        "correct_answer": "いっかげつ",
        "other_answers": [
            "ひとつ",
            "いちだい",
            "いちまい",
            "ひとり",
            "いっしゅうかん",
            "いっかい",
            "いちねん",
            "いちにち",
            "いっぱい",
            "いっさつ",
            "いっぽん",
            "いっぴき",
            "いっとう",
            "いちわ",
            "いちじかん",
            "いっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 56,
        "question": "２・かげつ",
        "correct_answer": "にかげつ",
        "other_answers": [
            "ふたつ",
            "にだい",
            "にまい",
            "ふたり",
            "にじゅうかん",
            "にかい",
            "にねん",
            "ふつか",
            "にはい",
            "にさつ",
            "にほん",
            "にひき",
            "にとう",
            "にわ",
            "にじかん",
            "にふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 57,
        "question": "３・かげつ",
        "correct_answer": "さんかげつ",
        "other_answers": [
            "みっつ",
            "さんだい",
            "さんまい",
            "さんにん",
            "さんしゅうかん",
            "さんかい",
            "さんねん",
            "みっか",
            "さんばい",
            "さんさつ",
            "さんぼん",
            "さんびき",
            "さんとう",
            "さんわ",
            "さんじかん",
            "さんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 58,
        "question": "４・かげつ",
        "correct_answer": "よんかげつ",
        "other_answers": [
            "よっつ",
            "よんだい",
            "よんまい",
            "よにん",
            "よんじゅうかん",
            "よんかい",
            "よんねん",
            "よっか",
            "よんはい",
            "よんさつ",
            "よんほん",
            "よんひき",
            "よんとう",
            "よんわ",
            "よじかん",
            "よんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 59,
        "question": "５・かげつ",
        "correct_answer": "ごかげつ",
        "other_answers": [
            "いつつ",
            "ごだい",
            "ごまい",
            "ごにん",
            "ごじゅうかん",
            "ごかい",
            "ごねん",
            "いつか",
            "ごはい",
            "ごさつ",
            "ごほん",
            "ごひき",
            "ごとう",
            "ごわ",
            "ごじかん",
            "ごふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 60,
        "question": "６・かげつ",
        "correct_answer": "ろっかげつ",
        "other_answers": [
            "むっつ",
            "ろくだい",
            "ろくまい",
            "ろくにん",
            "ろくしゅうかん",
            "ろっかい",
            "ろくねん",
            "むいか",
            "ろっぱい",
            "ろくさつ",
            "ろっぽん",
            "ろっぴき",
            "ろくとう",
            "ろくわ",
            "ろくじかん",
            "ろくぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 61,
        "question": "７・かげつ",
        "correct_answer": "ななかげつ・しちかげつ",
        "other_answers": [
            "ななつ",
            "ななだい",
            "ななまい",
            "ななにん・しちにん",
            "ななしゅうかん",
            "ななかい",
            "ななねん",
            "なのか",
            "ななはい",
            "ななさつ",
            "ななほん",
            "ななひき",
            "ななとう",
            "ななわ",
            "しちじかん",
            "ななふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 62,
        "question": "８・かげつ",
        "correct_answer": "はっかげつ",
        "other_answers": [
            "やっつ",
            "はちだい",
            "はちまい",
            "はちにん",
            "はっしゅうかん",
            "はっかい",
            "はちねん",
            "ようか",
            "はっぱい",
            "はっさつ",
            "はっぽん",
            "はっぴき",
            "はっとう",
            "はちわ",
            "はちじかん",
            "はっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 63,
        "question": "９・かげつ",
        "correct_answer": "きゅうかげつ",
        "other_answers": [
            "ここのつ",
            "きゅうだい",
            "きゅうまい",
            "きゅうにん",
            "きゅうしゅうかん",
            "きゅうかい",
            "きゅうねん",
            "ここのか",
            "きゅうはい",
            "きゅうさつ",
            "きゅうほん",
            "きゅうひき",
            "きゅうとう",
            "きゅうわ",
            "くじかん",
            "きゅうふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 64,
        "question": "１０・かげつ",
        "correct_answer": "じゅっかげつ",
        "other_answers": [
            "とお",
            "じゅうだい",
            "じゅうまい",
            "じゅうにん",
            "じゅっしゅうかん",
            "じゅっかい",
            "じゅうねん",
            "とおか",
            "じっぱい",
            "じっさつ",
            "じっぽん",
            "じっぴき",
            "じっとう",
            "じゅうわ",
            "じゅうじかん",
            "しゅうっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 65,
        "question": "？・かげつ",
        "correct_answer": "なんかげつ",
        "other_answers": [
            "いくつ",
            "なんだい",
            "なんまい",
            "なんにん",
            "なんしゅうかん",
            "なんかい",
            "なんねん",
            "なんにち",
            "なんばい",
            "なんさつ",
            "なんぼん",
            "なんびき",
            "なんとう",
            "なんわ",
            "なんじかん",
            "なんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 66,
        "question": "１・かい",
        "correct_answer": "いっかい",
        "other_answers": [
            "ひとつ",
            "いちだい",
            "いちまい",
            "ひとり",
            "いっしゅうかん",
            "いっかげつ",
            "いちねん",
            "いちにち",
            "いっぱい",
            "いっさつ",
            "いっぽん",
            "いっぴき",
            "いっとう",
            "いちわ",
            "いちじかん",
            "いっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 67,
        "question": "２・かい",
        "correct_answer": "にかい",
        "other_answers": [
            "ふたつ",
            "にだい",
            "にまい",
            "ふたり",
            "にじゅうかん",
            "にかげつ",
            "にねん",
            "ふつか",
            "にはい",
            "にさつ",
            "にほん",
            "にひき",
            "にとう",
            "にわ",
            "にじかん",
            "にふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 68,
        "question": "３・かい",
        "correct_answer": "さんかい",
        "other_answers": [
            "みっつ",
            "さんだい",
            "さんまい",
            "さんにん",
            "さんしゅうかん",
            "さんかげつ",
            "さんねん",
            "みっか",
            "さんばい",
            "さんさつ",
            "さんぼん",
            "さんびき",
            "さんとう",
            "さんわ",
            "さんじかん",
            "さんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 69,
        "question": "４・かい",
        "correct_answer": "よんかい",
        "other_answers": [
            "よっつ",
            "よんだい",
            "よんまい",
            "よにん",
            "よんじゅうかん",
            "よんかげつ",
            "よんねん",
            "よっか",
            "よんはい",
            "よんさつ",
            "よんほん",
            "よんひき",
            "よんとう",
            "よんわ",
            "よじかん",
            "よんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 70,
        "question": "５・かい",
        "correct_answer": "ごかい",
        "other_answers": [
            "いつつ",
            "ごだい",
            "ごまい",
            "ごにん",
            "ごじゅうかん",
            "ごかげつ",
            "ごねん",
            "いつか",
            "ごはい",
            "ごさつ",
            "ごほん",
            "ごひき",
            "ごとう",
            "ごわ",
            "ごじかん",
            "ごふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 71,
        "question": "６・かい",
        "correct_answer": "ろっかい",
        "other_answers": [
            "むっつ",
            "ろくだい",
            "ろくまい",
            "ろくにん",
            "ろくしゅうかん",
            "ろっかげつ",
            "ろくねん",
            "むいか",
            "ろっぱい",
            "ろくさつ",
            "ろっぽん",
            "ろっぴき",
            "ろくとう",
            "ろくわ",
            "ろくじかん",
            "ろくぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 72,
        "question": "７・かい",
        "correct_answer": "ななかい",
        "other_answers": [
            "ななつ",
            "ななだい",
            "ななまい",
            "ななにん・しちにん",
            "ななしゅうかん",
            "ななかげつ・しちかげつ",
            "ななねん",
            "なのか",
            "ななはい",
            "ななさつ",
            "ななほん",
            "ななひき",
            "ななとう",
            "ななわ",
            "しちじかん",
            "ななふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 73,
        "question": "８・かい",
        "correct_answer": "はっかい",
        "other_answers": [
            "やっつ",
            "はちだい",
            "はちまい",
            "はちにん",
            "はっしゅうかん",
            "はっかげつ",
            "はちねん",
            "ようか",
            "はっぱい",
            "はっさつ",
            "はっぽん",
            "はっぴき",
            "はっとう",
            "はちわ",
            "はちじかん",
            "はっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 74,
        "question": "９・かい",
        "correct_answer": "きゅうかい",
        "other_answers": [
            "ここのつ",
            "きゅうだい",
            "きゅうまい",
            "きゅうにん",
            "きゅうしゅうかん",
            "きゅうかげつ",
            "きゅうねん",
            "ここのか",
            "きゅうはい",
            "きゅうさつ",
            "きゅうほん",
            "きゅうひき",
            "きゅうとう",
            "きゅうわ",
            "くじかん",
            "きゅうふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 75,
        "question": "１０・かい",
        "correct_answer": "じゅっかい",
        "other_answers": [
            "とお",
            "じゅうだい",
            "じゅうまい",
            "じゅうにん",
            "じゅっしゅうかん",
            "じゅっかげつ",
            "じゅうねん",
            "とおか",
            "じっぱい",
            "じっさつ",
            "じっぽん",
            "じっぴき",
            "じっとう",
            "じゅうわ",
            "じゅうじかん",
            "しゅうっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 76,
        "question": "？・かい",
        "correct_answer": "なんかい",
        "other_answers": [
            "いくつ",
            "なんだい",
            "なんまい",
            "なんにん",
            "なんしゅうかん",
            "なんかげつ",
            "なんねん",
            "なんにち",
            "なんばい",
            "なんさつ",
            "なんぼん",
            "なんびき",
            "なんとう",
            "なんわ",
            "なんじかん",
            "なんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 77,
        "question": "１・ねん",
        "correct_answer": "いちねん",
        "other_answers": [
            "ひとつ",
            "いちだい",
            "いちまい",
            "ひとり",
            "いっしゅうかん",
            "いっかげつ",
            "いっかい",
            "いちにち",
            "いっぱい",
            "いっさつ",
            "いっぽん",
            "いっぴき",
            "いっとう",
            "いちわ",
            "いちじかん",
            "いっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 78,
        "question": "２・ねん",
        "correct_answer": "にねん",
        "other_answers": [
            "ふたつ",
            "にだい",
            "にまい",
            "ふたり",
            "にじゅうかん",
            "にかげつ",
            "にかい",
            "ふつか",
            "にはい",
            "にさつ",
            "にほん",
            "にひき",
            "にとう",
            "にわ",
            "にじかん",
            "にふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 79,
        "question": "３・ねん",
        "correct_answer": "さんねん",
        "other_answers": [
            "みっつ",
            "さんだい",
            "さんまい",
            "さんにん",
            "さんしゅうかん",
            "さんかげつ",
            "さんかい",
            "みっか",
            "さんばい",
            "さんさつ",
            "さんぼん",
            "さんびき",
            "さんとう",
            "さんわ",
            "さんじかん",
            "さんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 80,
        "question": "４・ねん",
        "correct_answer": "よんねん",
        "other_answers": [
            "よっつ",
            "よんだい",
            "よんまい",
            "よにん",
            "よんじゅうかん",
            "よんかげつ",
            "よんかい",
            "よっか",
            "よんはい",
            "よんさつ",
            "よんほん",
            "よんひき",
            "よんとう",
            "よんわ",
            "よじかん",
            "よんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 81,
        "question": "５・ねん",
        "correct_answer": "ごねん",
        "other_answers": [
            "いつつ",
            "ごだい",
            "ごまい",
            "ごにん",
            "ごじゅうかん",
            "ごかげつ",
            "ごかい",
            "いつか",
            "ごはい",
            "ごさつ",
            "ごほん",
            "ごひき",
            "ごとう",
            "ごわ",
            "ごじかん",
            "ごふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 82,
        "question": "６・ねん",
        "correct_answer": "ろくねん",
        "other_answers": [
            "むっつ",
            "ろくだい",
            "ろくまい",
            "ろくにん",
            "ろくしゅうかん",
            "ろっかげつ",
            "ろっかい",
            "むいか",
            "ろっぱい",
            "ろくさつ",
            "ろっぽん",
            "ろっぴき",
            "ろくとう",
            "ろくわ",
            "ろくじかん",
            "ろくぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 83,
        "question": "７・ねん",
        "correct_answer": "ななねん",
        "other_answers": [
            "ななつ",
            "ななだい",
            "ななまい",
            "ななにん・しちにん",
            "ななしゅうかん",
            "ななかげつ・しちかげつ",
            "ななかい",
            "なのか",
            "ななはい",
            "ななさつ",
            "ななほん",
            "ななひき",
            "ななとう",
            "ななわ",
            "しちじかん",
            "ななふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 84,
        "question": "８・ねん",
        "correct_answer": "はちねん",
        "other_answers": [
            "やっつ",
            "はちだい",
            "はちまい",
            "はちにん",
            "はっしゅうかん",
            "はっかげつ",
            "はっかい",
            "ようか",
            "はっぱい",
            "はっさつ",
            "はっぽん",
            "はっぴき",
            "はっとう",
            "はちわ",
            "はちじかん",
            "はっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 85,
        "question": "９・ねん",
        "correct_answer": "きゅうねん",
        "other_answers": [
            "ここのつ",
            "きゅうだい",
            "きゅうまい",
            "きゅうにん",
            "きゅうしゅうかん",
            "きゅうかげつ",
            "きゅうかい",
            "ここのか",
            "きゅうはい",
            "きゅうさつ",
            "きゅうほん",
            "きゅうひき",
            "きゅうとう",
            "きゅうわ",
            "くじかん",
            "きゅうふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 86,
        "question": "１０・ねん",
        "correct_answer": "じゅうねん",
        "other_answers": [
            "とお",
            "じゅうだい",
            "じゅうまい",
            "じゅうにん",
            "じゅっしゅうかん",
            "じゅっかげつ",
            "じゅっかい",
            "とおか",
            "じっぱい",
            "じっさつ",
            "じっぽん",
            "じっぴき",
            "じっとう",
            "じゅうわ",
            "じゅうじかん",
            "しゅうっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 87,
        "question": "？・ねん",
        "correct_answer": "なんねん",
        "other_answers": [
            "いくつ",
            "なんだい",
            "なんまい",
            "なんにん",
            "なんしゅうかん",
            "なんかげつ",
            "なんかい",
            "なんにち",
            "なんばい",
            "なんさつ",
            "なんぼん",
            "なんびき",
            "なんとう",
            "なんわ",
            "なんじかん",
            "なんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 88,
        "question": "１・にち",
        "correct_answer": "いちにち",
        "other_answers": [
            "ひとつ",
            "いちだい",
            "いちまい",
            "ひとり",
            "いっしゅうかん",
            "いっかげつ",
            "いっかい",
            "いちねん",
            "いっぱい",
            "いっさつ",
            "いっぽん",
            "いっぴき",
            "いっとう",
            "いちわ",
            "いちじかん",
            "いっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 89,
        "question": "２・にち",
        "correct_answer": "ふつか",
        "other_answers": [
            "ふたつ",
            "にだい",
            "にまい",
            "ふたり",
            "にじゅうかん",
            "にかげつ",
            "にかい",
            "にねん",
            "にはい",
            "にさつ",
            "にほん",
            "にひき",
            "にとう",
            "にわ",
            "にじかん",
            "にふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 90,
        "question": "３・にち",
        "correct_answer": "みっか",
        "other_answers": [
            "みっつ",
            "さんだい",
            "さんまい",
            "さんにん",
            "さんしゅうかん",
            "さんかげつ",
            "さんかい",
            "さんねん",
            "さんばい",
            "さんさつ",
            "さんぼん",
            "さんびき",
            "さんとう",
            "さんわ",
            "さんじかん",
            "さんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 91,
        "question": "４・にち",
        "correct_answer": "よっか",
        "other_answers": [
            "よっつ",
            "よんだい",
            "よんまい",
            "よにん",
            "よんじゅうかん",
            "よんかげつ",
            "よんかい",
            "よんねん",
            "よんはい",
            "よんさつ",
            "よんほん",
            "よんひき",
            "よんとう",
            "よんわ",
            "よじかん",
            "よんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 92,
        "question": "５・にち",
        "correct_answer": "いつか",
        "other_answers": [
            "いつつ",
            "ごだい",
            "ごまい",
            "ごにん",
            "ごじゅうかん",
            "ごかげつ",
            "ごかい",
            "ごねん",
            "ごはい",
            "ごさつ",
            "ごほん",
            "ごひき",
            "ごとう",
            "ごわ",
            "ごじかん",
            "ごふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 93,
        "question": "６・にち",
        "correct_answer": "むいか",
        "other_answers": [
            "むっつ",
            "ろくだい",
            "ろくまい",
            "ろくにん",
            "ろくしゅうかん",
            "ろっかげつ",
            "ろっかい",
            "ろくねん",
            "ろっぱい",
            "ろくさつ",
            "ろっぽん",
            "ろっぴき",
            "ろくとう",
            "ろくわ",
            "ろくじかん",
            "ろくぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 94,
        "question": "７・にち",
        "correct_answer": "なのか",
        "other_answers": [
            "ななつ",
            "ななだい",
            "ななまい",
            "ななにん・しちにん",
            "ななしゅうかん",
            "ななかげつ・しちかげつ",
            "ななかい",
            "ななねん",
            "ななはい",
            "ななさつ",
            "ななほん",
            "ななひき",
            "ななとう",
            "ななわ",
            "しちじかん",
            "ななふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 95,
        "question": "８・にち",
        "correct_answer": "ようか",
        "other_answers": [
            "やっつ",
            "はちだい",
            "はちまい",
            "はちにん",
            "はっしゅうかん",
            "はっかげつ",
            "はっかい",
            "はちねん",
            "はっぱい",
            "はっさつ",
            "はっぽん",
            "はっぴき",
            "はっとう",
            "はちわ",
            "はちじかん",
            "はっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 96,
        "question": "９・にち",
        "correct_answer": "ここのか",
        "other_answers": [
            "ここのつ",
            "きゅうだい",
            "きゅうまい",
            "きゅうにん",
            "きゅうしゅうかん",
            "きゅうかげつ",
            "きゅうかい",
            "きゅうねん",
            "きゅうはい",
            "きゅうさつ",
            "きゅうほん",
            "きゅうひき",
            "きゅうとう",
            "きゅうわ",
            "くじかん",
            "きゅうふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 97,
        "question": "１０・にち",
        "correct_answer": "とおか",
        "other_answers": [
            "とお",
            "じゅうだい",
            "じゅうまい",
            "じゅうにん",
            "じゅっしゅうかん",
            "じゅっかげつ",
            "じゅっかい",
            "じゅうねん",
            "じっぱい",
            "じっさつ",
            "じっぽん",
            "じっぴき",
            "じっとう",
            "じゅうわ",
            "じゅうじかん",
            "しゅうっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 98,
        "question": "？・にち",
        "correct_answer": "なんにち",
        "other_answers": [
            "いくつ",
            "なんだい",
            "なんまい",
            "なんにん",
            "なんしゅうかん",
            "なんかげつ",
            "なんかい",
            "なんねん",
            "なんばい",
            "なんさつ",
            "なんぼん",
            "なんびき",
            "なんとう",
            "なんわ",
            "なんじかん",
            "なんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 99,
        "question": "１・みす",
        "correct_answer": "いっぱい",
        "other_answers": [
            "ひとつ",
            "いちだい",
            "いちまい",
            "ひとり",
            "いっしゅうかん",
            "いっかげつ",
            "いっかい",
            "いちねん",
            "いちにち",
            "いっさつ",
            "いっぽん",
            "いっぴき",
            "いっとう",
            "いちわ",
            "いちじかん",
            "いっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 100,
        "question": "２・みす",
        "correct_answer": "にはい",
        "other_answers": [
            "ふたつ",
            "にだい",
            "にまい",
            "ふたり",
            "にじゅうかん",
            "にかげつ",
            "にかい",
            "にねん",
            "ふつか",
            "にさつ",
            "にほん",
            "にひき",
            "にとう",
            "にわ",
            "にじかん",
            "にふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 101,
        "question": "３・コーヒー",
        "correct_answer": "さんばい",
        "other_answers": [
            "みっつ",
            "さんだい",
            "さんまい",
            "さんにん",
            "さんしゅうかん",
            "さんかげつ",
            "さんかい",
            "さんねん",
            "みっか",
            "さんさつ",
            "さんぼん",
            "さんびき",
            "さんとう",
            "さんわ",
            "さんじかん",
            "さんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 102,
        "question": "４・コーヒー",
        "correct_answer": "よんはい",
        "other_answers": [
            "よっつ",
            "よんだい",
            "よんまい",
            "よにん",
            "よんじゅうかん",
            "よんかげつ",
            "よんかい",
            "よんねん",
            "よっか",
            "よんさつ",
            "よんほん",
            "よんひき",
            "よんとう",
            "よんわ",
            "よじかん",
            "よんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 103,
        "question": "５・コーヒー",
        "correct_answer": "ごはい",
        "other_answers": [
            "いつつ",
            "ごだい",
            "ごまい",
            "ごにん",
            "ごじゅうかん",
            "ごかげつ",
            "ごかい",
            "ごねん",
            "いつか",
            "ごさつ",
            "ごほん",
            "ごひき",
            "ごとう",
            "ごわ",
            "ごじかん",
            "ごふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 104,
        "question": "６・みす",
        "correct_answer": "ろっぱい",
        "other_answers": [
            "むっつ",
            "ろくだい",
            "ろくまい",
            "ろくにん",
            "ろくしゅうかん",
            "ろっかげつ",
            "ろっかい",
            "ろくねん",
            "むいか",
            "ろくさつ",
            "ろっぽん",
            "ろっぴき",
            "ろくとう",
            "ろくわ",
            "ろくじかん",
            "ろくぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 105,
        "question": "７・みす",
        "correct_answer": "ななはい",
        "other_answers": [
            "ななつ",
            "ななだい",
            "ななまい",
            "ななにん・しちにん",
            "ななしゅうかん",
            "ななかげつ・しちかげつ",
            "ななかい",
            "ななねん",
            "なのか",
            "ななさつ",
            "ななほん",
            "ななひき",
            "ななとう",
            "ななわ",
            "しちじかん",
            "ななふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 106,
        "question": "８・コーヒー",
        "correct_answer": "はっぱい",
        "other_answers": [
            "やっつ",
            "はちだい",
            "はちまい",
            "はちにん",
            "はっしゅうかん",
            "はっかげつ",
            "はっかい",
            "はちねん",
            "ようか",
            "はっさつ",
            "はっぽん",
            "はっぴき",
            "はっとう",
            "はちわ",
            "はちじかん",
            "はっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 107,
        "question": "９・みす",
        "correct_answer": "きゅうはい",
        "other_answers": [
            "ここのつ",
            "きゅうだい",
            "きゅうまい",
            "きゅうにん",
            "きゅうしゅうかん",
            "きゅうかげつ",
            "きゅうかい",
            "きゅうねん",
            "ここのか",
            "きゅうさつ",
            "きゅうほん",
            "きゅうひき",
            "きゅうとう",
            "きゅうわ",
            "くじかん",
            "きゅうふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 108,
        "question": "１０・みす",
        "correct_answer": "じっぱい",
        "other_answers": [
            "とお",
            "じゅうだい",
            "じゅうまい",
            "じゅうにん",
            "じゅっしゅうかん",
            "じゅっかげつ",
            "じゅっかい",
            "じゅうねん",
            "とおか",
            "じっさつ",
            "じっぽん",
            "じっぴき",
            "じっとう",
            "じゅうわ",
            "じゅうじかん",
            "しゅうっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 109,
        "question": "？・みす",
        "correct_answer": "なんばい",
        "other_answers": [
            "いくつ",
            "なんだい",
            "なんまい",
            "なんにん",
            "なんしゅうかん",
            "なんかげつ",
            "なんかい",
            "なんねん",
            "なんにち",
            "なんさつ",
            "なんぼん",
            "なんびき",
            "なんとう",
            "なんわ",
            "なんじかん",
            "なんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 110,
        "question": "１・ほん",
        "correct_answer": "いっさつ",
        "other_answers": [
            "ひとつ",
            "いちだい",
            "いちまい",
            "ひとり",
            "いっしゅうかん",
            "いっかげつ",
            "いっかい",
            "いちねん",
            "いちにち",
            "いっぱい",
            "いっぽん",
            "いっぴき",
            "いっとう",
            "いちわ",
            "いちじかん",
            "いっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 111,
        "question": "２・ざっし",
        "correct_answer": "にさつ",
        "other_answers": [
            "ふたつ",
            "にだい",
            "にまい",
            "ふたり",
            "にじゅうかん",
            "にかげつ",
            "にかい",
            "にねん",
            "ふつか",
            "にはい",
            "にほん",
            "にひき",
            "にとう",
            "にわ",
            "にじかん",
            "にふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 112,
        "question": "３・ざっし",
        "correct_answer": "さんさつ",
        "other_answers": [
            "みっつ",
            "さんだい",
            "さんまい",
            "さんにん",
            "さんしゅうかん",
            "さんかげつ",
            "さんかい",
            "さんねん",
            "みっか",
            "さんばい",
            "さんぼん",
            "さんびき",
            "さんとう",
            "さんわ",
            "さんじかん",
            "さんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 113,
        "question": "４・ほん",
        "correct_answer": "よんさつ",
        "other_answers": [
            "よっつ",
            "よんだい",
            "よんまい",
            "よにん",
            "よんじゅうかん",
            "よんかげつ",
            "よんかい",
            "よんねん",
            "よっか",
            "よんはい",
            "よんほん",
            "よんひき",
            "よんとう",
            "よんわ",
            "よじかん",
            "よんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 114,
        "question": "５・ほん",
        "correct_answer": "ごさつ",
        "other_answers": [
            "いつつ",
            "ごだい",
            "ごまい",
            "ごにん",
            "ごじゅうかん",
            "ごかげつ",
            "ごかい",
            "ごねん",
            "いつか",
            "ごはい",
            "ごほん",
            "ごひき",
            "ごとう",
            "ごわ",
            "ごじかん",
            "ごふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 115,
        "question": "６・ほん",
        "correct_answer": "ろくさつ",
        "other_answers": [
            "むっつ",
            "ろくだい",
            "ろくまい",
            "ろくにん",
            "ろくしゅうかん",
            "ろっかげつ",
            "ろっかい",
            "ろくねん",
            "むいか",
            "ろっぱい",
            "ろっぽん",
            "ろっぴき",
            "ろくとう",
            "ろくわ",
            "ろくじかん",
            "ろくぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 116,
        "question": "７・ざっし",
        "correct_answer": "ななさつ",
        "other_answers": [
            "ななつ",
            "ななだい",
            "ななまい",
            "ななにん・しちにん",
            "ななしゅうかん",
            "ななかげつ・しちかげつ",
            "ななかい",
            "ななねん",
            "なのか",
            "ななはい",
            "ななほん",
            "ななひき",
            "ななとう",
            "ななわ",
            "しちじかん",
            "ななふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 117,
        "question": "８・ほん",
        "correct_answer": "はっさつ",
        "other_answers": [
            "やっつ",
            "はちだい",
            "はちまい",
            "はちにん",
            "はっしゅうかん",
            "はっかげつ",
            "はっかい",
            "はちねん",
            "ようか",
            "はっぱい",
            "はっぽん",
            "はっぴき",
            "はっとう",
            "はちわ",
            "はちじかん",
            "はっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 118,
        "question": "９・ざっし",
        "correct_answer": "きゅうさつ",
        "other_answers": [
            "ここのつ",
            "きゅうだい",
            "きゅうまい",
            "きゅうにん",
            "きゅうしゅうかん",
            "きゅうかげつ",
            "きゅうかい",
            "きゅうねん",
            "ここのか",
            "きゅうはい",
            "きゅうほん",
            "きゅうひき",
            "きゅうとう",
            "きゅうわ",
            "くじかん",
            "きゅうふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 119,
        "question": "１０・ざっし",
        "correct_answer": "じっさつ",
        "other_answers": [
            "とお",
            "じゅうだい",
            "じゅうまい",
            "じゅうにん",
            "じゅっしゅうかん",
            "じゅっかげつ",
            "じゅっかい",
            "じゅうねん",
            "とおか",
            "じっぱい",
            "じっぽん",
            "じっぴき",
            "じっとう",
            "じゅうわ",
            "じゅうじかん",
            "しゅうっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 120,
        "question": "？・ほん",
        "correct_answer": "なんさつ",
        "other_answers": [
            "いくつ",
            "なんだい",
            "なんまい",
            "なんにん",
            "なんしゅうかん",
            "なんかげつ",
            "なんかい",
            "なんねん",
            "なんにち",
            "なんばい",
            "なんぼん",
            "なんびき",
            "なんとう",
            "なんわ",
            "なんじかん",
            "なんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 121,
        "question": "１・えんぴつ",
        "correct_answer": "いっぽん",
        "other_answers": [
            "ひとつ",
            "いちだい",
            "いちまい",
            "ひとり",
            "いっしゅうかん",
            "いっかげつ",
            "いっかい",
            "いちねん",
            "いちにち",
            "いっぱい",
            "いっさつ",
            "いっぴき",
            "いっとう",
            "いちわ",
            "いちじかん",
            "いっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 122,
        "question": "２・ぺん",
        "correct_answer": "にほん",
        "other_answers": [
            "ふたつ",
            "にだい",
            "にまい",
            "ふたり",
            "にじゅうかん",
            "にかげつ",
            "にかい",
            "にねん",
            "ふつか",
            "にはい",
            "にさつ",
            "にひき",
            "にとう",
            "にわ",
            "にじかん",
            "にふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 123,
        "question": "３・かさ",
        "correct_answer": "さんぼん",
        "other_answers": [
            "みっつ",
            "さんだい",
            "さんまい",
            "さんにん",
            "さんしゅうかん",
            "さんかげつ",
            "さんかい",
            "さんねん",
            "みっか",
            "さんばい",
            "さんさつ",
            "さんびき",
            "さんとう",
            "さんわ",
            "さんじかん",
            "さんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 124,
        "question": "４・えんぴつ",
        "correct_answer": "よんほん",
        "other_answers": [
            "よっつ",
            "よんだい",
            "よんまい",
            "よにん",
            "よんじゅうかん",
            "よんかげつ",
            "よんかい",
            "よんねん",
            "よっか",
            "よんはい",
            "よんさつ",
            "よんひき",
            "よんとう",
            "よんわ",
            "よじかん",
            "よんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 125,
        "question": "５・ぺん",
        "correct_answer": "ごほん",
        "other_answers": [
            "いつつ",
            "ごだい",
            "ごまい",
            "ごにん",
            "ごじゅうかん",
            "ごかげつ",
            "ごかい",
            "ごねん",
            "いつか",
            "ごはい",
            "ごさつ",
            "ごひき",
            "ごとう",
            "ごわ",
            "ごじかん",
            "ごふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 126,
        "question": "６・ぺん",
        "correct_answer": "ろっぽん",
        "other_answers": [
            "むっつ",
            "ろくだい",
            "ろくまい",
            "ろくにん",
            "ろくしゅうかん",
            "ろっかげつ",
            "ろっかい",
            "ろくねん",
            "むいか",
            "ろっぱい",
            "ろくさつ",
            "ろっぴき",
            "ろくとう",
            "ろくわ",
            "ろくじかん",
            "ろくぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 127,
        "question": "７・ぺん",
        "correct_answer": "ななほん",
        "other_answers": [
            "ななつ",
            "ななだい",
            "ななまい",
            "ななにん・しちにん",
            "ななしゅうかん",
            "ななかげつ・しちかげつ",
            "ななかい",
            "ななねん",
            "なのか",
            "ななはい",
            "ななさつ",
            "ななひき",
            "ななとう",
            "ななわ",
            "しちじかん",
            "ななふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 128,
        "question": "８・ぺん",
        "correct_answer": "はっぽん",
        "other_answers": [
            "やっつ",
            "はちだい",
            "はちまい",
            "はちにん",
            "はっしゅうかん",
            "はっかげつ",
            "はっかい",
            "はちねん",
            "ようか",
            "はっぱい",
            "はっさつ",
            "はっぴき",
            "はっとう",
            "はちわ",
            "はちじかん",
            "はっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 129,
        "question": "９・ぺん",
        "correct_answer": "きゅうほん",
        "other_answers": [
            "ここのつ",
            "きゅうだい",
            "きゅうまい",
            "きゅうにん",
            "きゅうしゅうかん",
            "きゅうかげつ",
            "きゅうかい",
            "きゅうねん",
            "ここのか",
            "きゅうはい",
            "きゅうさつ",
            "きゅうひき",
            "きゅうとう",
            "きゅうわ",
            "くじかん",
            "きゅうふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 130,
        "question": "１０・えんぴつ",
        "correct_answer": "じっぽん",
        "other_answers": [
            "とお",
            "じゅうだい",
            "じゅうまい",
            "じゅうにん",
            "じゅっしゅうかん",
            "じゅっかげつ",
            "じゅっかい",
            "じゅうねん",
            "とおか",
            "じっぱい",
            "じっさつ",
            "じっぴき",
            "じっとう",
            "じゅうわ",
            "じゅうじかん",
            "しゅうっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 131,
        "question": "？・かさ",
        "correct_answer": "なんぼん",
        "other_answers": [
            "いくつ",
            "なんだい",
            "なんまい",
            "なんにん",
            "なんしゅうかん",
            "なんかげつ",
            "なんかい",
            "なんねん",
            "なんにち",
            "なんばい",
            "なんさつ",
            "なんびき",
            "なんとう",
            "なんわ",
            "なんじかん",
            "なんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 132,
        "question": "１・ねこ",
        "correct_answer": "いっぴき",
        "other_answers": [
            "ひとつ",
            "いちだい",
            "いちまい",
            "ひとり",
            "いっしゅうかん",
            "いっかげつ",
            "いっかい",
            "いちねん",
            "いちにち",
            "いっぱい",
            "いっさつ",
            "いっぽん",
            "いっとう",
            "いちわ",
            "いちじかん",
            "いっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 133,
        "question": "２・ねこ",
        "correct_answer": "にひき",
        "other_answers": [
            "ふたつ",
            "にだい",
            "にまい",
            "ふたり",
            "にじゅうかん",
            "にかげつ",
            "にかい",
            "にねん",
            "ふつか",
            "にはい",
            "にさつ",
            "にほん",
            "にとう",
            "にわ",
            "にじかん",
            "にふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 134,
        "question": "３・ねこ",
        "correct_answer": "さんびき",
        "other_answers": [
            "みっつ",
            "さんだい",
            "さんまい",
            "さんにん",
            "さんしゅうかん",
            "さんかげつ",
            "さんかい",
            "さんねん",
            "みっか",
            "さんばい",
            "さんさつ",
            "さんぼん",
            "さんとう",
            "さんわ",
            "さんじかん",
            "さんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 135,
        "question": "４・いぬ",
        "correct_answer": "よんひき",
        "other_answers": [
            "よっつ",
            "よんだい",
            "よんまい",
            "よにん",
            "よんじゅうかん",
            "よんかげつ",
            "よんかい",
            "よんねん",
            "よっか",
            "よんはい",
            "よんさつ",
            "よんほん",
            "よんとう",
            "よんわ",
            "よじかん",
            "よんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 136,
        "question": "５・いぬ",
        "correct_answer": "ごひき",
        "other_answers": [
            "いつつ",
            "ごだい",
            "ごまい",
            "ごにん",
            "ごじゅうかん",
            "ごかげつ",
            "ごかい",
            "ごねん",
            "いつか",
            "ごはい",
            "ごさつ",
            "ごほん",
            "ごとう",
            "ごわ",
            "ごじかん",
            "ごふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 137,
        "question": "６・ねこ",
        "correct_answer": "ろっぴき",
        "other_answers": [
            "むっつ",
            "ろくだい",
            "ろくまい",
            "ろくにん",
            "ろくしゅうかん",
            "ろっかげつ",
            "ろっかい",
            "ろくねん",
            "むいか",
            "ろっぱい",
            "ろくさつ",
            "ろっぽん",
            "ろくとう",
            "ろくわ",
            "ろくじかん",
            "ろくぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 138,
        "question": "７・いぬ",
        "correct_answer": "ななひき",
        "other_answers": [
            "ななつ",
            "ななだい",
            "ななまい",
            "ななにん・しちにん",
            "ななしゅうかん",
            "ななかげつ・しちかげつ",
            "ななかい",
            "ななねん",
            "なのか",
            "ななはい",
            "ななさつ",
            "ななほん",
            "ななとう",
            "ななわ",
            "しちじかん",
            "ななふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 139,
        "question": "８・ねこ",
        "correct_answer": "はっぴき",
        "other_answers": [
            "やっつ",
            "はちだい",
            "はちまい",
            "はちにん",
            "はっしゅうかん",
            "はっかげつ",
            "はっかい",
            "はちねん",
            "ようか",
            "はっぱい",
            "はっさつ",
            "はっぽん",
            "はっとう",
            "はちわ",
            "はちじかん",
            "はっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 140,
        "question": "９・いぬ",
        "correct_answer": "きゅうひき",
        "other_answers": [
            "ここのつ",
            "きゅうだい",
            "きゅうまい",
            "きゅうにん",
            "きゅうしゅうかん",
            "きゅうかげつ",
            "きゅうかい",
            "きゅうねん",
            "ここのか",
            "きゅうはい",
            "きゅうさつ",
            "きゅうほん",
            "きゅうとう",
            "きゅうわ",
            "くじかん",
            "きゅうふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 141,
        "question": "１０・ねこ",
        "correct_answer": "じっぴき",
        "other_answers": [
            "とお",
            "じゅうだい",
            "じゅうまい",
            "じゅうにん",
            "じゅっしゅうかん",
            "じゅっかげつ",
            "じゅっかい",
            "じゅうねん",
            "とおか",
            "じっぱい",
            "じっさつ",
            "じっぽん",
            "じっとう",
            "じゅうわ",
            "じゅうじかん",
            "しゅうっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 142,
        "question": "？・いぬ",
        "correct_answer": "なんびき",
        "other_answers": [
            "いくつ",
            "なんだい",
            "なんまい",
            "なんにん",
            "なんしゅうかん",
            "なんかげつ",
            "なんかい",
            "なんねん",
            "なんにち",
            "なんばい",
            "なんさつ",
            "なんぼん",
            "なんとう",
            "なんわ",
            "なんじかん",
            "なんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 143,
        "question": "１・パンダ",
        "correct_answer": "いっとう",
        "other_answers": [
            "ひとつ",
            "いちだい",
            "いちまい",
            "ひとり",
            "いっしゅうかん",
            "いっかげつ",
            "いっかい",
            "いちねん",
            "いちにち",
            "いっぱい",
            "いっさつ",
            "いっぽん",
            "いっぴき",
            "いちわ",
            "いちじかん",
            "いっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 144,
        "question": "２・うま",
        "correct_answer": "にとう",
        "other_answers": [
            "ふたつ",
            "にだい",
            "にまい",
            "ふたり",
            "にじゅうかん",
            "にかげつ",
            "にかい",
            "にねん",
            "ふつか",
            "にはい",
            "にさつ",
            "にほん",
            "にひき",
            "にわ",
            "にじかん",
            "にふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 145,
        "question": "３・くま",
        "correct_answer": "さんとう",
        "other_answers": [
            "みっつ",
            "さんだい",
            "さんまい",
            "さんにん",
            "さんしゅうかん",
            "さんかげつ",
            "さんかい",
            "さんねん",
            "みっか",
            "さんばい",
            "さんさつ",
            "さんぼん",
            "さんびき",
            "さんわ",
            "さんじかん",
            "さんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 146,
        "question": "４・うま",
        "correct_answer": "よんとう",
        "other_answers": [
            "よっつ",
            "よんだい",
            "よんまい",
            "よにん",
            "よんじゅうかん",
            "よんかげつ",
            "よんかい",
            "よんねん",
            "よっか",
            "よんはい",
            "よんさつ",
            "よんほん",
            "よんひき",
            "よんわ",
            "よじかん",
            "よんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 147,
        "question": "５・パンダ",
        "correct_answer": "ごとう",
        "other_answers": [
            "いつつ",
            "ごだい",
            "ごまい",
            "ごにん",
            "ごじゅうかん",
            "ごかげつ",
            "ごかい",
            "ごねん",
            "いつか",
            "ごはい",
            "ごさつ",
            "ごほん",
            "ごひき",
            "ごわ",
            "ごじかん",
            "ごふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 148,
        "question": "６・くま",
        "correct_answer": "ろくとう",
        "other_answers": [
            "むっつ",
            "ろくだい",
            "ろくまい",
            "ろくにん",
            "ろくしゅうかん",
            "ろっかげつ",
            "ろっかい",
            "ろくねん",
            "むいか",
            "ろっぱい",
            "ろくさつ",
            "ろっぽん",
            "ろっぴき",
            "ろくわ",
            "ろくじかん",
            "ろくぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 149,
        "question": "７・パンダ",
        "correct_answer": "ななとう",
        "other_answers": [
            "ななつ",
            "ななだい",
            "ななまい",
            "ななにん・しちにん",
            "ななしゅうかん",
            "ななかげつ・しちかげつ",
            "ななかい",
            "ななねん",
            "なのか",
            "ななはい",
            "ななさつ",
            "ななほん",
            "ななひき",
            "ななわ",
            "しちじかん",
            "ななふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 150,
        "question": "８・ライオン",
        "correct_answer": "はっとう",
        "other_answers": [
            "やっつ",
            "はちだい",
            "はちまい",
            "はちにん",
            "はっしゅうかん",
            "はっかげつ",
            "はっかい",
            "はちねん",
            "ようか",
            "はっぱい",
            "はっさつ",
            "はっぽん",
            "はっぴき",
            "はちわ",
            "はちじかん",
            "はっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 151,
        "question": "９・うま",
        "correct_answer": "きゅうとう",
        "other_answers": [
            "ここのつ",
            "きゅうだい",
            "きゅうまい",
            "きゅうにん",
            "きゅうしゅうかん",
            "きゅうかげつ",
            "きゅうかい",
            "きゅうねん",
            "ここのか",
            "きゅうはい",
            "きゅうさつ",
            "きゅうほん",
            "きゅうひき",
            "きゅうわ",
            "くじかん",
            "きゅうふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 152,
        "question": "１０・パンダ",
        "correct_answer": "じっとう",
        "other_answers": [
            "とお",
            "じゅうだい",
            "じゅうまい",
            "じゅうにん",
            "じゅっしゅうかん",
            "じゅっかげつ",
            "じゅっかい",
            "じゅうねん",
            "とおか",
            "じっぱい",
            "じっさつ",
            "じっぽん",
            "じっぴき",
            "じゅうわ",
            "じゅうじかん",
            "しゅうっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 153,
        "question": "？・うま",
        "correct_answer": "なんとう",
        "other_answers": [
            "いくつ",
            "なんだい",
            "なんまい",
            "なんにん",
            "なんしゅうかん",
            "なんかげつ",
            "なんかい",
            "なんねん",
            "なんにち",
            "なんばい",
            "なんさつ",
            "なんぼん",
            "なんびき",
            "なんわ",
            "なんじかん",
            "なんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 154,
        "question": "１・うさぎ",
        "correct_answer": "いちわ",
        "other_answers": [
            "ひとつ",
            "いちだい",
            "いちまい",
            "ひとり",
            "いっしゅうかん",
            "いっかげつ",
            "いっかい",
            "いちねん",
            "いちにち",
            "いっぱい",
            "いっさつ",
            "いっぽん",
            "いっぴき",
            "いっとう",
            "いちじかん",
            "いっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 155,
        "question": "２・とり",
        "correct_answer": "にわ",
        "other_answers": [
            "ふたつ",
            "にだい",
            "にまい",
            "ふたり",
            "にじゅうかん",
            "にかげつ",
            "にかい",
            "にねん",
            "ふつか",
            "にはい",
            "にさつ",
            "にほん",
            "にひき",
            "にとう",
            "にじかん",
            "にふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 156,
        "question": "３・とり",
        "correct_answer": "さんわ",
        "other_answers": [
            "みっつ",
            "さんだい",
            "さんまい",
            "さんにん",
            "さんしゅうかん",
            "さんかげつ",
            "さんかい",
            "さんねん",
            "みっか",
            "さんばい",
            "さんさつ",
            "さんぼん",
            "さんびき",
            "さんとう",
            "さんじかん",
            "さんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 157,
        "question": "４・とり",
        "correct_answer": "よんわ",
        "other_answers": [
            "よっつ",
            "よんだい",
            "よんまい",
            "よにん",
            "よんじゅうかん",
            "よんかげつ",
            "よんかい",
            "よんねん",
            "よっか",
            "よんはい",
            "よんさつ",
            "よんほん",
            "よんひき",
            "よんとう",
            "よじかん",
            "よんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 158,
        "question": "５・うさぎ",
        "correct_answer": "ごわ",
        "other_answers": [
            "いつつ",
            "ごだい",
            "ごまい",
            "ごにん",
            "ごじゅうかん",
            "ごかげつ",
            "ごかい",
            "ごねん",
            "いつか",
            "ごはい",
            "ごさつ",
            "ごほん",
            "ごひき",
            "ごとう",
            "ごじかん",
            "ごふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 159,
        "question": "６・とり",
        "correct_answer": "ろくわ",
        "other_answers": [
            "むっつ",
            "ろくだい",
            "ろくまい",
            "ろくにん",
            "ろくしゅうかん",
            "ろっかげつ",
            "ろっかい",
            "ろくねん",
            "むいか",
            "ろっぱい",
            "ろくさつ",
            "ろっぽん",
            "ろっぴき",
            "ろくとう",
            "ろくじかん",
            "ろくぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 160,
        "question": "７・うさぎ",
        "correct_answer": "ななわ",
        "other_answers": [
            "ななつ",
            "ななだい",
            "ななまい",
            "ななにん・しちにん",
            "ななしゅうかん",
            "ななかげつ・しちかげつ",
            "ななかい",
            "ななねん",
            "なのか",
            "ななはい",
            "ななさつ",
            "ななほん",
            "ななひき",
            "ななとう",
            "しちじかん",
            "ななふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 161,
        "question": "８・とり",
        "correct_answer": "はちわ",
        "other_answers": [
            "やっつ",
            "はちだい",
            "はちまい",
            "はちにん",
            "はっしゅうかん",
            "はっかげつ",
            "はっかい",
            "はちねん",
            "ようか",
            "はっぱい",
            "はっさつ",
            "はっぽん",
            "はっぴき",
            "はっとう",
            "はちじかん",
            "はっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 162,
        "question": "９・とり",
        "correct_answer": "きゅうわ",
        "other_answers": [
            "ここのつ",
            "きゅうだい",
            "きゅうまい",
            "きゅうにん",
            "きゅうしゅうかん",
            "きゅうかげつ",
            "きゅうかい",
            "きゅうねん",
            "ここのか",
            "きゅうはい",
            "きゅうさつ",
            "きゅうほん",
            "きゅうひき",
            "きゅうとう",
            "くじかん",
            "きゅうふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 163,
        "question": "１０・とり",
        "correct_answer": "じゅうわ",
        "other_answers": [
            "とお",
            "じゅうだい",
            "じゅうまい",
            "じゅうにん",
            "じゅっしゅうかん",
            "じゅっかげつ",
            "じゅっかい",
            "じゅうねん",
            "とおか",
            "じっぱい",
            "じっさつ",
            "じっぽん",
            "じっぴき",
            "じっとう",
            "じゅうじかん",
            "しゅうっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 164,
        "question": "？・とり",
        "correct_answer": "なんわ",
        "other_answers": [
            "いくつ",
            "なんだい",
            "なんまい",
            "なんにん",
            "なんしゅうかん",
            "なんかげつ",
            "なんかい",
            "なんねん",
            "なんにち",
            "なんばい",
            "なんさつ",
            "なんぼん",
            "なんびき",
            "なんとう",
            "なんじかん",
            "なんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 165,
        "question": "１・じかん",
        "correct_answer": "いちじかん",
        "other_answers": [
            "ひとつ",
            "いちだい",
            "いちまい",
            "ひとり",
            "いっしゅうかん",
            "いっかげつ",
            "いっかい",
            "いちねん",
            "いちにち",
            "いっぱい",
            "いっさつ",
            "いっぽん",
            "いっぴき",
            "いっとう",
            "いちわ",
            "いっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 166,
        "question": "２・じかん",
        "correct_answer": "にじかん",
        "other_answers": [
            "ふたつ",
            "にだい",
            "にまい",
            "ふたり",
            "にじゅうかん",
            "にかげつ",
            "にかい",
            "にねん",
            "ふつか",
            "にはい",
            "にさつ",
            "にほん",
            "にひき",
            "にとう",
            "にわ",
            "にふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 167,
        "question": "３・じかん",
        "correct_answer": "さんじかん",
        "other_answers": [
            "みっつ",
            "さんだい",
            "さんまい",
            "さんにん",
            "さんしゅうかん",
            "さんかげつ",
            "さんかい",
            "さんねん",
            "みっか",
            "さんばい",
            "さんさつ",
            "さんぼん",
            "さんびき",
            "さんとう",
            "さんわ",
            "さんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 168,
        "question": "４・じかん",
        "correct_answer": "よじかん",
        "other_answers": [
            "よっつ",
            "よんだい",
            "よんまい",
            "よにん",
            "よんじゅうかん",
            "よんかげつ",
            "よんかい",
            "よんねん",
            "よっか",
            "よんはい",
            "よんさつ",
            "よんほん",
            "よんひき",
            "よんとう",
            "よんわ",
            "よんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 169,
        "question": "５・じかん",
        "correct_answer": "ごじかん",
        "other_answers": [
            "いつつ",
            "ごだい",
            "ごまい",
            "ごにん",
            "ごじゅうかん",
            "ごかげつ",
            "ごかい",
            "ごねん",
            "いつか",
            "ごはい",
            "ごさつ",
            "ごほん",
            "ごひき",
            "ごとう",
            "ごわ",
            "ごふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 170,
        "question": "６・じかん",
        "correct_answer": "ろくじかん",
        "other_answers": [
            "むっつ",
            "ろくだい",
            "ろくまい",
            "ろくにん",
            "ろくしゅうかん",
            "ろっかげつ",
            "ろっかい",
            "ろくねん",
            "むいか",
            "ろっぱい",
            "ろくさつ",
            "ろっぽん",
            "ろっぴき",
            "ろくとう",
            "ろくわ",
            "ろくぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 171,
        "question": "７・じかん",
        "correct_answer": "しちじかん",
        "other_answers": [
            "ななつ",
            "ななだい",
            "ななまい",
            "ななにん・しちにん",
            "ななしゅうかん",
            "ななかげつ・しちかげつ",
            "ななかい",
            "ななねん",
            "なのか",
            "ななはい",
            "ななさつ",
            "ななほん",
            "ななひき",
            "ななとう",
            "ななわ",
            "ななふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 172,
        "question": "８・じかん",
        "correct_answer": "はちじかん",
        "other_answers": [
            "やっつ",
            "はちだい",
            "はちまい",
            "はちにん",
            "はっしゅうかん",
            "はっかげつ",
            "はっかい",
            "はちねん",
            "ようか",
            "はっぱい",
            "はっさつ",
            "はっぽん",
            "はっぴき",
            "はっとう",
            "はちわ",
            "はっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 173,
        "question": "９・じかん",
        "correct_answer": "くじかん",
        "other_answers": [
            "ここのつ",
            "きゅうだい",
            "きゅうまい",
            "きゅうにん",
            "きゅうしゅうかん",
            "きゅうかげつ",
            "きゅうかい",
            "きゅうねん",
            "ここのか",
            "きゅうはい",
            "きゅうさつ",
            "きゅうほん",
            "きゅうひき",
            "きゅうとう",
            "きゅうわ",
            "きゅうふん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 174,
        "question": "１０・じかん",
        "correct_answer": "じゅうじかん",
        "other_answers": [
            "とお",
            "じゅうだい",
            "じゅうまい",
            "じゅうにん",
            "じゅっしゅうかん",
            "じゅっかげつ",
            "じゅっかい",
            "じゅうねん",
            "とおか",
            "じっぱい",
            "じっさつ",
            "じっぽん",
            "じっぴき",
            "じっとう",
            "じゅうわ",
            "しゅうっぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 175,
        "question": "？・じかん",
        "correct_answer": "なんじかん",
        "other_answers": [
            "いくつ",
            "なんだい",
            "なんまい",
            "なんにん",
            "なんしゅうかん",
            "なんかげつ",
            "なんかい",
            "なんねん",
            "なんにち",
            "なんばい",
            "なんさつ",
            "なんぼん",
            "なんびき",
            "なんとう",
            "なんわ",
            "なんぷん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 176,
        "question": "１・ふん・ぷん",
        "correct_answer": "いっぷん",
        "other_answers": [
            "ひとつ",
            "いちだい",
            "いちまい",
            "ひとり",
            "いっしゅうかん",
            "いっかげつ",
            "いっかい",
            "いちねん",
            "いちにち",
            "いっぱい",
            "いっさつ",
            "いっぽん",
            "いっぴき",
            "いっとう",
            "いちわ",
            "いちじかん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 177,
        "question": "２・ふん・ぷん",
        "correct_answer": "にふん",
        "other_answers": [
            "ふたつ",
            "にだい",
            "にまい",
            "ふたり",
            "にじゅうかん",
            "にかげつ",
            "にかい",
            "にねん",
            "ふつか",
            "にはい",
            "にさつ",
            "にほん",
            "にひき",
            "にとう",
            "にわ",
            "にじかん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 178,
        "question": "３・ふん・ぷん",
        "correct_answer": "さんぷん",
        "other_answers": [
            "みっつ",
            "さんだい",
            "さんまい",
            "さんにん",
            "さんしゅうかん",
            "さんかげつ",
            "さんかい",
            "さんねん",
            "みっか",
            "さんばい",
            "さんさつ",
            "さんぼん",
            "さんびき",
            "さんとう",
            "さんわ",
            "さんじかん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 179,
        "question": "４・ふん・ぷん",
        "correct_answer": "よんぷん",
        "other_answers": [
            "よっつ",
            "よんだい",
            "よんまい",
            "よにん",
            "よんじゅうかん",
            "よんかげつ",
            "よんかい",
            "よんねん",
            "よっか",
            "よんはい",
            "よんさつ",
            "よんほん",
            "よんひき",
            "よんとう",
            "よんわ",
            "よじかん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 180,
        "question": "５・ふん・ぷん",
        "correct_answer": "ごふん",
        "other_answers": [
            "いつつ",
            "ごだい",
            "ごまい",
            "ごにん",
            "ごじゅうかん",
            "ごかげつ",
            "ごかい",
            "ごねん",
            "いつか",
            "ごはい",
            "ごさつ",
            "ごほん",
            "ごひき",
            "ごとう",
            "ごわ",
            "ごじかん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 181,
        "question": "６・ふん・ぷん",
        "correct_answer": "ろくぷん",
        "other_answers": [
            "むっつ",
            "ろくだい",
            "ろくまい",
            "ろくにん",
            "ろくしゅうかん",
            "ろっかげつ",
            "ろっかい",
            "ろくねん",
            "むいか",
            "ろっぱい",
            "ろくさつ",
            "ろっぽん",
            "ろっぴき",
            "ろくとう",
            "ろくわ",
            "ろくじかん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 182,
        "question": "７・ふん・ぷん",
        "correct_answer": "ななふん",
        "other_answers": [
            "ななつ",
            "ななだい",
            "ななまい",
            "ななにん・しちにん",
            "ななしゅうかん",
            "ななかげつ・しちかげつ",
            "ななかい",
            "ななねん",
            "なのか",
            "ななはい",
            "ななさつ",
            "ななほん",
            "ななひき",
            "ななとう",
            "ななわ",
            "しちじかん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 183,
        "question": "８・ふん・ぷん",
        "correct_answer": "はっぷん",
        "other_answers": [
            "やっつ",
            "はちだい",
            "はちまい",
            "はちにん",
            "はっしゅうかん",
            "はっかげつ",
            "はっかい",
            "はちねん",
            "ようか",
            "はっぱい",
            "はっさつ",
            "はっぽん",
            "はっぴき",
            "はっとう",
            "はちわ",
            "はちじかん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 184,
        "question": "９・ふん・ぷん",
        "correct_answer": "きゅうふん",
        "other_answers": [
            "ここのつ",
            "きゅうだい",
            "きゅうまい",
            "きゅうにん",
            "きゅうしゅうかん",
            "きゅうかげつ",
            "きゅうかい",
            "きゅうねん",
            "ここのか",
            "きゅうはい",
            "きゅうさつ",
            "きゅうほん",
            "きゅうひき",
            "きゅうとう",
            "きゅうわ",
            "くじかん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 185,
        "question": "１０・ふん・ぷん",
        "correct_answer": "しゅうっぷん",
        "other_answers": [
            "とお",
            "じゅうだい",
            "じゅうまい",
            "じゅうにん",
            "じゅっしゅうかん",
            "じゅっかげつ",
            "じゅっかい",
            "じゅうねん",
            "とおか",
            "じっぱい",
            "じっさつ",
            "じっぽん",
            "じっぴき",
            "じっとう",
            "じゅうわ",
            "じゅうじかん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 186,
        "question": "？・ふん・ぷん",
        "correct_answer": "なんぷん",
        "other_answers": [
            "いくつ",
            "なんだい",
            "なんまい",
            "なんにん",
            "なんしゅうかん",
            "なんかげつ",
            "なんかい",
            "なんねん",
            "なんにち",
            "なんばい",
            "なんさつ",
            "なんぼん",
            "なんびき",
            "なんとう",
            "なんわ",
            "なんじかん"
        ]
    }
]